<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="app_name">agram</string>
  <string name="about_word_list">
    The following applies to the word list,
    which is taken from the Spell Checking Oriented Word Lists (SCOWL).
    \n\n
      Copyright 2000-2015 by Kevin Atkinson
    \n\n
      Permission to use, copy, modify, distribute and sell these word
      lists, the associated scripts, the output created from the scripts,
      and its documentation for any purpose is hereby granted without fee,
      provided that the above copyright notice appears in all copies and
      that both that copyright notice and this permission notice appear in
      supporting documentation. Kevin Atkinson makes no representations
      about the suitability of this array for any purpose. It is provided
      "as is" without express or implied warranty.
    \n\n
    The WordNet database, which was used in the creation of the
    Inflections database, is under the following copyright:
    \n\n
      This software and database is being provided to you, the LICENSEE,
      by Princeton University under the following license.  By obtaining,
      using and/or copying this software and database, you agree that you
      have read, understood, and will comply with these terms and
      conditions.:
    \n\n
      Permission to use, copy, modify and distribute this software and
      database and its documentation for any purpose and without fee or
      royalty is hereby granted, provided that you agree to comply with
      the following copyright notice and statements, including the
      disclaimer, and that the same appear on ALL copies of the software,
      database and documentation, including modifications that you make
      for internal use or for distribution.
    \n\n
      WordNet 1.6 Copyright 1997 by Princeton University.  All rights
      reserved.
    \n\n
      THIS SOFTWARE AND DATABASE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND PRINCETON
      UNIVERSITY MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR
      IMPLIED.  BY WAY OF EXAMPLE, BUT NOT LIMITATION, PRINCETON
      UNIVERSITY MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF MERCHANT-
      ABILITY OR FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR THAT THE USE OF THE
      LICENSED SOFTWARE, DATABASE OR DOCUMENTATION WILL NOT INFRINGE ANY
      THIRD PARTY PATENTS, COPYRIGHTS, TRADEMARKS OR OTHER RIGHTS.
    \n\n
      The name of Princeton University or Princeton may not be used in
      advertising or publicity pertaining to distribution of the software
      and/or database.  Title to copyright in this software, database and
      any associated documentation shall at all times remain with
      Princeton University and LICENSEE agrees to preserve same.
  </string>
  <string name="about_icons">
    Some icons are reproduced from work created and shared by the Android Open Source Project and used according to terms described in the Creative Commons 2.5 Attribution License.
  </string>
  <string name="about_code">
    Copyright (c) 2013, 2014, 2015 Charles Cagle
    \n\n
    Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
    of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
    in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
    to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
    copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
    furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
    \n\n
    The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
    copies or substantial portions of the Software.
    \n\n
    THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
    IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
    FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
    AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
    LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
    OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
    SOFTWARE.
  </string>
</resources>
